ethplorer.io 2017-09-09

# Ethplorer — Privacy & Terms

******Terms**

Ethplorer, Everex. Ptd ("Ethplorer") owns and operates [https://ethplorer.io/](https://ethplorer.io/) and permits you to access the site under the following terms and conditions. By signing up to use Ethplorer through the site, view tokens developed with the ethereum ERC20 standard, explore contract supply, sender, receiver, and amount of transaction in token units or use any features available on or through the Site, you, plus any entity that you represent, are agreeing to the terms below.

You represent and warrant that you are older than 18 years. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use the Ethplorer Service. Ethplorer may, in its sole discretion, refuse to offer the service to any person or entity and change its eligibility criteria at any time.

You represent and warrant that you: are of legal age to form a binding contract; have not previously been suspended or removed from using our Services; and have full power and authority to enter into this agreement and in doing so will not violate any other agreement to which you are a party.

To access the service, you may be required to create an account with Ethplorer. You need to provide accurate and complete information and keep your account information updated. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account, and for keeping your account password secure. You may never use another person's user account or registration information without permission. You must notify Ethplorer immediately of any change in your eligibility to use Ethplorer services (including any changes to or revocation of any licenses from state authorities), or of any discovered or otherwise suspected breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.

To update or fix Ethplorer tokens, you may be required to provide your email, name of token, token contract address, symbol of token, decimals and social media profiles. You are solely responsible for changes that occurs on your token information. You may never use another person's token information without permission. Ethplorer does not currently charge fees for updating or fixing your Ethplorer token, however we reserve the right to do so in future, and in such case any applicable fees will be displayed prior to you using any Service to which a fee applies.

If you want to view tokens or contract supply, sender, receiver, and amount of transaction in token units, you will be required to visit the Site and, in certain cases, enter applicable information. Where relevant, if we determine that the information you provide is correct, we will permit you to continue and find an information.

You may not use the service to create any data that might be competitive with or aggressive toward the Ethplorer service.

You may not use the Ethplorer service in any way that damages any law, governance or control, including any reason identified as money-laundering or terrorist activities.

You may not lease or rent the Service, or generally use Ethplorer Services for timesharing or administration authority purposes, or for the advantage of middlemen.

Some options of the service may be available simplest via your purchase, and we reserve the right to refuse any order for such features. If the occasion arises we need to make an alternative order, we will attempt to notify you via e-mail. Please note that costs might be changed at any time and that we can be required by regulation to apply income tax on certain orders.

With regards to billing, we use a third-party payment processor (the "payment processor") to invoice you via a charge account linked in your account at the offerings (your "billing account") for the purchase. The processing of payments could be be subject to the terms, conditions and privacy policies of the payment processor in addition to those terms. We are not liable for errors by the processor. By means of selecting to make any purchase, you authorize us to charge you via the payment processor in accordance with the relevant price terms.

You agree that we may also have the right to terminate your ability to access the web site for violations of any of these terms. We may additionally terminate your ability to obtain entry to the web site at any time, without or with reason, with or without notice, effective without delay, which can also result in the forfeiture and destruction of all token informations related to your account, consisting of without problem, all data. if you want to terminate your account, you may do so by using following the rules on the website. All provisions of these terms which by means of their nature should live on termination shall continue to exist termination, inclusive of, without problem, ownership provisions, assurance disclaimers, indemnifications and boundaries of legal responsibility.

Ethplorer shall not have any duty below this agreement to provide any improvements, patches, enhancements, fixes or any other assistance to you for Ethplorer services. You can contact Ethplorer support via our website, but we do not make any promise or guarantee it will be able to repair any trouble you may be having. If Ethplorer presents you with any enhancements, patches, upgrades, or fixes for the Etplorer service, then the items which might be provided become a part of the service and subject to this settlement. Any suggestions or tips via Ethplorer regarding the provider shall not be construed as a warranty.

You agree that Ethplorer shall have no liability whatsoever for any use you make of the service. You hereby agree to indemnify and hold harmless Ethplorer from any and all claims, demands, damages, losses, liabilities, costs, and expenses (including attorney's fees) arising from or related to your use of the service.

Ethplorer has no special or unique relationship with you. You agree that Ethplorer doesn't control over and feature obligation to take any action concerning: which users get priority entry to the website; what type of information users get via the website; what effects or results the data may have on you; how you may interpret or use the data; or what actions or movements you may take as a result of having discovered the information. You exempt Ethplorer from liability for your having acquired or not acquired token information through the website. Ethplorer doesn't make any representations regarding any information placed on the website, and Ethplorer will not be responsible for the accuracy, legality or decency of information contained accessed through the website.

Ethplorer offers the opportunity for users to view token transactions or token with information, token balance and information on a smart contract. In using Ethplorer, you agree that third-parties may view your token transactions provided by the token transactions.

It is completely your choice as to how and with whom you share your token information. However, anyone with whom you have shared a tx hash, contract address, sender address is able to see that your token transaction through the Service.

In utilizing Ethplorer, you may see the information given by third parties, including connections to website pages and services of such parties ("third-party data"). We don't control, support or embrace any outsider information and will have no duty regarding third-party data, including, without constraint, material that might misdirect, deficient, incorrect, hostile or generally offensive in your jurisdiction. In addition, your business dealings or correspondence with such third parties are solely between you and the third parties. We are not dependable or obligated for any misfortune or harm of any kind brought about as the consequence of any such dealings, and you comprehend that your using of third-party content, and your connections with the third-parties, is at your own risk.

Unless in any other case indicated by using Ethplorer, all copyright and other intellectual property rights in all content material and different substances contained on the website or supplied in connection with Ethplorer, such as, without limitation, the company or corporation brand and all designs, content, graphics, software, other files and the choice and arrangement thereof (together, "company materials") are the proprietary property of Ethplorer or our licensors or providers and are protected by means of copyright legal guidelines and different intellectual property rights laws. We hereby furnish you a restricted, nonexclusive and non-sublicensable license to get right of entry to and use the company materials to your personal or commercial enterprise use. Such license is subject to these terms and does no longer allow (i) any resale of the Ethplorer products; (ii) the distribution, public performance or public show of any company materials; (iii) enhancing or in any other case making any spinoff makes use of of the company materials, or any portion thereof; or (iv) any use of the company materials apart from for their intended functions.

Ethplorer shall not be responsible or liable for the content or for any data, liability, damages or expenses caused and or suffered as a result of any use of information of the token on this website.

Ethplorer and its directors, employees, agents, affiliates, parents and subsidiaries don't warrant that: (i) Ethplorer will be secure or available at any time: (ii) any errors will be corrected; (iii) Ethplorer services are or will be free of viruses; or (iv) your use of and access to the website and service will meet your requirements or expectations.  
You acknowledge and warrant that information you transfer through Ethplorer may become lost or corrupted or temporarily unavailable because of a variety of causes, including software failures, protocol modifications by third party provides, internet outages, force majeure or other scheduled or unscheduled maintenance or other causes within or outside Ethplorer's control. You are solely responsible for backing up and maintaining duplicate copies of any information you transfer through Ethplorer. Your use of Ethplorer is solely at your own risk.

In no event are Ethplorer and its directors, employees, agents, affiliates, parents and subsidiaries liable for any special, indirect or consequential damages, including loss of data or resulting from reliance by any user on any information obtained from Ethplore or transmission or any failure of performance.

You agree that we may change these terms, suspend or discontinue the Ethplorer service at any time by posting an update to the website and by sending you an e-mail. We may also impose limits on certain features and services or restrict your access to parts or all of the site without notice. To check the terms periodically is your responsibility. If you continue to use the service following any changes to the terms, it means your accepting those changes. If you do not agree to any changed to the terms, kindly discontinue using the website.

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy depicts the arrangements and systems of Everex ("Ethplorer") on the accumulation, using and revelation of your data on the <https://ethplorer.io/> (the "site") and the administrations, applications, and different components or usefulness accessible on or through the Ethplorer site (all things considered, the "service").

We recommend you to read our privacy policy to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information in accordance with the website.

_Collecting of Personal Information - What Personal Information does Ethplorer collect?_

When you enroll for the Service, you may be asked to enter your personal information such as your name, username, password, and email address. You recognize that this data is personal to you, and by showing a token on Ethplorer, you permit others, including Ethplorer, to distinguish you. We collect your contact information to send you about the Ethplorer service. You may unsubscribe from beyond any doubt of these messages through bearings on the site, however, certain exchanges, for instance, basic data concerning the Service are not subject to unsubscription. To the degree you outfit Ethplorer with individual information, you are not anonymous to us.

Ethplorer may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For instance, when you update your Ethplorer token via a third-party service, we may collect information about your social media accounts in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such service, including your public profile, friend list and email address.

Ethplorer is primarily intended to assist you to view the token information in a smart contract on the ethereum blockchain. The data that you provide to us is information that we will need in order to provide that service.

Ethplorer does not at present gather money-related data regarding your payment method (e.g., valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information) when you pay our service on the Site. This data is gathered and put away by our outsider installment handling organization (the "Payment Processor"), and utilize and capacity of that data is represented by the Payment Processor's relevant terms of service and privacy policy.

Ethplorer gets and stores certain sorts of data at whatever point you interface with the service. It naturally receives and records data on our server logs from your program including your IP address and the page you requested.

_How does Ethplorer use your personal data?_

We may use your personal information we collect from you when you may register, make purchases via the service, browse the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: to improve users' experience and to let us to deliver the right type of content and product offerings in which you may be most interested; to manage and develop our business and operations; to let us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests; to develop new and enhance existing service and product offerings;

Ethplorer also reserves the right to use aggregated Personal Data provided that those data do not relate to any individual.  
Personal Data may be collected, stored and/or processed by companies in the Everex corporate family to perform functions on our behalf. All such third parties will be contractually bound to protect data in compliance with our policy.

Ethplorer will process your Personal Data legally and fairly and not use it outside the purposes of which the service have informed you. So far as the service is able Ethplorer shall ensure that all of your Personal Data is accurate and up to date.

_Is Your Personal Information Secure?_

You protect your Ethplorer account personal information by your password. You need to thwart unapproved access to your account and personal information by selecting and ensuring your password fittingly and compelling access to your computer device and browser by shutting down after you have finished your account.

Ethplorer protects personal information with appropriate physical, technological and organizational safeguards and security measures. Your personal information comes to the service via the internet which chooses its own routes and means whereby information is conveyed from location to location. As such Ethplorer cannot give any warranty or guarantee that the means where information is conveyed to us are safe, reliable or have integrity

Ethplorer may change this Privacy Policy from at any time. Any changes will be posted so that you are always aware of what information Ethplorer collects and how the service uses it.
